<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[CrunchTime]]></title><description><![CDATA[My blog description]]></description><link>https://Afrokillaa.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 21:34:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Welcome to CrunchTime]]></title><description><![CDATA[About me As I don’t want to dox myself, I will not be giving you guys my full name, but you can call me Afrokilla. I’m also known as…]]></description><link>https://Afrokillaa.github.io/first_post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://Afrokillaa.github.io/first_post/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;About me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I don’t want to dox myself, I will not be giving you guys my full name, but you can call me &lt;strong&gt;Afrokilla&lt;/strong&gt;. I’m also known as afrokilla#8343 on Discord and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/afrokilla&quot;&gt;@afrokilla&lt;/a&gt; on Twitter. Yes, I’m that guy who spams giveaways and comments, but I also post about up-and-coming NFT projects (sometimes). Anyway, I work as a programmer with a degree in computer science engineering and after my day job I spend most of my time on Discord servers grinding for those whitelists and minting/trading NFTs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Why I started this blog&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had been thinking of starting a blog for a while now, initially it would be more related to programming and feature tutorials and stuff, but I recently amassed a huge Twitter following of &lt;strong&gt;103 people&lt;/strong&gt; with my crypto account and felt I cannot disappoint my loyal followers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel there is much gatekeeping in the space, especially for people new to NFTs &amp;#x26; crypto. For myself it was also difficult to get started, hard to find new projects, to get whitelisted, to know if a project was good or not. Luckily, by random chance, I met some great guys in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RetroWolvesNFT&quot;&gt;RetroWolves&lt;/a&gt; discord voice chat. One thing led to another and we made or own “Alpha Discord” to discuss projects, share alpha, and crack some jokes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have learned much more from our small community than I would have ever learned on my own in the same timeframe. It essentially allows everyone involved to benefit from each other’s research and experience. Therefore, I started this blog to help people find good projects, tools, and resources. I want to be that “friend” to aid you through your Web3 journey and perhaps build a small community of likeminded people on my Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;So what content can we expect?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The focus of the blog will be on Decentralized Finance (DeFi), mainly focused on NFTs, Web3 and how it works, and a bit of programming &amp;#x26; tutorials to interact with Web3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write-ups about new NFT projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tools and resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;News from the NFT space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basics of crypto &amp;#x26; NFTs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Web3 programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;A work in progress&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, the blog still has some bugs &amp;#x26; glitches, but I’m working on it. I felt it was time to start writing instead of coding and setting everything up. I hope you will follow me through my Web3 journey, learn some new things, and perhaps make some new friends 😄&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To stay updated on my latest posts, follow my Twitter or subscribe to the blog below&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>